go go go go let's go
走走走走走 我们走走
sh police Health
shsh警察卫生署
checkup Health checkup
卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查 卫生检查
健康检查
checkup Health checkup
Center I'm so healthy I'm not worried at
健康健康检查中心 我很健康 我不担心
中心,我这么健康,我不担心
Center I'm so healthy I'm not worried at
all let's
中心,我身体健康,我完全不担心
让我们一起
all let's
start I'm going to check your height
开始吧,我检查你的身高
我开始检查你的身高
start I'm going to check your height
who's first me I'll go first
我开始检查你的身高 谁是第一个我 我先走
oh you got taller really
哦,你变高了,真的
mhm I got taller
哦,你变高了,我变高了,我变高了
awesome look at
看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊,看啊
this I got taller
看看这个,我变高了
这个我更高了
this I got taller
too what how's that
这下我也有高高了,那又怎样?
那又怎样呢?
too what how's that
possible
可能(可能)
doy you need to stand straight like me
跟我一样站直一点
I got
我拿到了
it you guys are the same
我知道你们是同一类人
你们俩是同一个人
it you guys are the same
height let's check your weight
你们是同一身高 让我们检查一下体重
身高,让我们检查你的体重
height let's check your weight
okay good
身高高,让我们检查你的体重,好
良好但无
okay good
next
下一个
good it's my
下一好,这是我的
好,这是我的
good it's my
turn
转转
overweight what's wrong am I that heavy
转超重量,什么是错的 我那么重吗?
uh Doby don't hold anything when you
呃,多比没有 持有任何东西,当你
weigh
呃 多比当体重重时什么也拿不稳
称重
weigh
yourself oh I forgot anything else let
我忘了别的什么,让我来
哦,我忘记了别的事
yourself oh I forgot anything else let
me see oh I bought this
哦,我忘了其他任何东西 让我看看,哦,我买了这个
你看我,我买了这个
me see oh I bought this
today yesterday me before last
我看见我,哦,我今天买了这个 今天昨天我之前买的
今天昨天我昨天在最后一天之前
today yesterday me before last
week last month aha all
上星期 上个月啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊
clear it's done great B
很明显,它做了伟大的B
normal now I'll check your
清楚了,做得很好,B正常 现在,我会检查你的
正常,现在我会检查你
normal now I'll check your
mouth
正常,现在我检查你的嘴唇
uh you have very healthy teeth
你有很健康的牙齿
sir your teeth are healthy too
你的牙齿也健康
great mine will be healthy
你的牙齿很健康 我的太伟大了,我的会很健康
我的伟大矿将健康健康
great mine will be healthy
too oh it looks like a cavity what let
哦,它看起来像一个洞洞,什么让
me check
哦,它看起来像一个洞洞 让我检查一下
我检查
me check
again some food stuck in there always
总是有些食物卡在里面
keep your teeth
里面又塞着一些食物 总是保持你的牙齿
保持牙齿
keep your teeth
clean I forgot to
保持你的牙齿干净,我忘记了
干净我忘记了
clean I forgot to
brush hearing test right left up right
右左向右左向上刷刷听觉测试
left right left up heart and lungs check
右左左左右右右右左左左 心脏和肺部检查
心脏和肺部检查
left right left up heart and lungs check
you're fine
左左左左心心 肺部检查,你没事
good no
良好无
heartbeat it's my phone alarm sorry let
心跳,这是我的电话报警声 对不起,让
me check
心跳,这是我的电话报警声 对不起,让我检查一下
我检查
me check
again all good the knee Turk reflex
我再次检查所有好 膝盖土耳其反射
膝盖的反射,土耳其式的膝盖反射
again all good the knee Turk reflex
test ouch
AUT 测试测试器
time for your vision
时间到你的视力的时候,
test what letter is
时间来测试什么是字母
测试什么是字母
test what letter is
this L switch
测试哪个字母是这个 L 开关
此 L 开关
this L switch
sides this
LL 切换这一边
边 边 边 边 边 边
sides this
one
这一边的这一边
1个
one
C wow great eyesight how
一C哇伟大的视力如何
哇,伟大的视力如何
C wow great eyesight how
about this
哇,伟大的视力 如何这样
与此相关的
about this
one that's
有关这个...
其中一个是
one that's
easy w
一个很简单的W
简单 W
easy w
good
简单 w 好
良好
good
job now the smell test what do you smell
工作,现在的气味测试 你闻什么气味
Apple avocado and
你闻到什么味道 苹果鳄梨和
苹果鳄梨和
Apple avocado and
this juice made with strawberries
苹果鳄梨和用草莓做的果汁
这个果汁是用草莓做的
this juice made with strawberries
watermelon and two cherries
这是用草莓西瓜和两个樱桃做的果汁
西瓜和两樱桃
watermelon and two cherries
perfect
西瓜和两樱桃完美无缺
wow the last checkup the breathing test
呼吸测试的最后一次检查
blow up the balloon in one breath please
请将气球一口气炸开
test complete you guys are
测试完成,你们是
healthy
测试完成,你们身体健康
awesome Sheriff's note things to keep in
好棒警长的笔记 {\fn黑体\fs22\bord1\shad0\3aHBE\4aH00\fscx67\fscy66\2cHFFFFFF\3cH
mind kids regular checkups are very
孩子们经常做定期体检很正常
important they help us know if we're in
孩子们定期体检很重要 他们能帮我们知道我们是否在
重要的是他们能帮助我们知道 我们是否在
important they help us know if we're in
good
重要的是他们能帮助我们知道我们是否安好
良好
good
health if there's a problem it can be
如果有问题的话 健康健康
如果有问题,健康健康 它可以是
health if there's a problem it can be
treated in time to keep us
如果有问题 可以及时治疗 来留住我们
及时治疗,以便我们永居。
treated in time to keep us
healthy the growing
健康成长
nose your T-Rex
鼻子的T-Rex
W your
鼻子的TRX W 你的TRX W
W 妇女( W)
W your
tricerat you're pcia Shar
{\fn黑体\fs22\bord1\shad0\3aHBE\4aH00\fscx67\fscy66\2cHFFFFFF\3cH2F2F2F {\fn黑体\fs22\bord1\shad0\3aHBE\4aH00\fscx67\fscy66\2cHFFFFFF\3cH2F2F2F
awesome I want want two y dinos I want
我要两双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双双
the biggest one oops
我要两双双双双双双双双双双双双,我要最大的一双双
ouch oh
哦
no my big
# 没有我的大 # # # 没有我的大 # # # No my big # # # no my big #
dinosaur dinosaur my Maroons oh no no no
恐龙恐龙我的马龙... 哦,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,恐恐恐恐恐恐恐恐恐恐恐恐恐恐恐恐龙,我的马龙,哦,哦,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不
watch
恐龙恐龙我的马龙... 哦,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,
out Sher Labrador someone popped my Dino
谢尔拉布拉多 有人把我的迪诺打爆了
balloons help me
沙尔拉布拉多 有人爆了我的迪诺气球 帮我一把
气球帮助我
balloons help me
please do you know who did
你知道是谁干的吗?
it
其 其 年 , 其 年 , 其 年 , 其
no h must be one of
必须是其中之一
h 必须是
no h must be one of
you no not me sir someone is
一定不是你们的人 不是我 先生 有人是
不,你不是我,先生,先生,有人是
you no not me sir someone is
lying don't worry we'll figure it out
先生 有人在撒谎 别担心 我们会想出办法的
骗骗你不用担心 我们会想出办法的
lying don't worry we'll figure it out
who could it be I don't
骗骗人不用担心 我们会找出来是谁的 我不
know are you telling the truth Pinocchio
你知道你说的是真话吗? 皮诺曹
if you lie your nose will grow I'm not
你知道你说的是真话吗? 皮诺曹,如果你撒谎,你的鼻子会长大
如果你撒谎,你的鼻子会长起来 我不会的
if you lie your nose will grow I'm not
lying I didn't take the Apple
如果你说谎,你的鼻子会长大 我没有说谎,我没有拿苹果
no who popped the balloon who
谁没有弹出气球 谁没有弹出气球谁
didn't Wei do you
魏伟没有杀你吗?
know I I don't know
魏伟难道不知道吗 你知道我不知道
我知道我不知道,我不知道
know I I don't know
your
贵国的
nose my nose got
鼻子鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻鼻
longer oh no everyone will know I lied
哦,不是每个人都会知道我撒谎了
when they look at my
哦,不是每个人都会 知道我说谎 当他们看着我,
nose pippy rabbit do you know who pop
你知道是谁弹的吗?
the
排
balloons I I don't know not me anyway
气球,我不认识 我不认识我,反正
oh my
哦,我的,哦,我的
goodness my nose it's getting
我的鼻子,我的鼻子,我的鼻子 它得到
longer oh keep you
天啊,我的鼻子越来越长了哦,你留着吧
更久哦 保持你
longer oh keep you
rabbit oops don't see me do you know who
保持你兔子 眼不见我,你知道是谁吗?
兔子眼眼没看见我,你知道是谁吗?
rabbit oops don't see me do you know who
popped the
兔子圈没看见我,你知道是谁跳的吗?
balloons I I don't
气球 我不
know that
(知道)知道
hurts thirsty oh I'm going to buy a
口渴,哦,我要买
drake
德拉克
oh wow look guys his nose is really long
他鼻子好长啊,好长啊,好长啊,帅哥,他的鼻子好长啊
哇,看伙计们,他的鼻子真的很长
oh wow look guys his nose is really long
he must have lied
哇,看伙计们,他的鼻子真的很长 他一定是撒了谎
oh
哦
no
哦,不,哦,不
无 无
no
ouch long
没有长的,没有长的
nose he's a liar he's a
他是一个骗子,他是一个
liar no I'm not
我不是骗子,我不是骗子
winner is Mr
胜者是先生
sloth
时间空档
baby pey
贝贝贝贝贝贝贝贝贝贝贝贝贝贝贝贝贝贝贝贝贝贝贝贝贝
rabbit Danger
贝贝贝贝比兔子危险
兔子危险
rabbit Danger
oh my nose come on peee rabbit wake
兔子危险哦,我的鼻子 来在小兔子唤醒
up my nose got longer and longer your
我的鼻子上鼻子 越长越长,你越长
nose it looks
我鼻子的鼻子长了,你的鼻子长了,它看起来
看着鼻子的鼻子
nose it looks
fine my nose is
我的鼻子细细的鼻子
fine thank goodness it was just a
谢天谢地,那只是
谢谢天谢地,它只是一个
fine thank goodness it was just a
dream I I'm sorry I popped the balloons
我梦到,对不起,我把气球打爆了
by
梦见我对不起我把气球打爆了
至
by
mistake we already knew that we found
我们早已知道我们发现
我们已经知道我们发现了错误
mistake we already knew that we found
this at the
我们已经知道 我们发现这个错误
),在
this at the
scene it's your lollipop right yes I
在现场的这个 这是你的棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒
就是你的棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒棒 右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右
scene it's your lollipop right yes I
tripped and the balloons popped it was
是的,我绊倒了,气球弹响了
气球弹出气球
tripped and the balloons popped it was
an
气球弹出气球
a , a , a , a , a , a
an
accident I'm glad you told the truth I
我很高兴你说了实话
意外 我很高兴你说了实话
accident I'm glad you told the truth I
forgive you
意外 我很高兴你说实话 我原谅你
than all
超过所有
done wow this one is even cooler I want
哇,这个更酷,我更想要
哇,这个更酷,我想要
done wow this one is even cooler I want
one too be careful don't pop the
哇,这个更酷 我想要一个也小心点,不要弹出
balloons Sheriff's notes things to keep
气球警长的笔记要保存
in
气球警长的笔记
内
in
mind kids everyone makes mistakes
每个人都会犯错
每个人犯错都犯错
mind kids everyone makes mistakes
sometimes lying won't make your nose
小孩 人人都会犯错 有时说谎不会让你的鼻子
有时说谎,不会让你的鼻子
sometimes lying won't make your nose
grow but it's very bad to make a mistake
有时说谎不会让你的鼻子长起来 但犯错是很坏的
长大了,但犯错是坏的
grow but it's very bad to make a mistake
and then lie about
但犯错误,然后撒谎 是非常糟糕的
然后,你当说谎,
and then lie about
it we should be brave to tell the truth
然后,我们为它而否认它,我们誓必勇敢地说出真理,
我们应该勇敢地说出真相
it we should be brave to tell the truth
and try to correct our
我们应该勇敢地说出真相 并试图纠正我们
并试图纠正
and try to correct our
mistakes this is is how we learn to
并试图纠正我们的错误 这就是我们如何学会
这就是我们如何学会的错误
mistakes this is is how we learn to
grow please remember
这就是我们如何学会成长的错误 请记住
that the key stealing
钥匙的偷盗
cat who's up for a mission this
谁的猫猫谁的 准备一个任务,这个
time wow
时间哇哇
me I have practiced lockpicking for 10
我练习了十次锁锁
我已经练习了十次锁锁的练习
me I have practiced lockpicking for 10
years
我练习了10年的锁锁 已经练习了10年了
年份
years
there's no luck that I can't
年复一年,没有运气,我无法
没有运气,我不能
there's no luck that I can't
open oh really I bet you can't open this
没有运气,我不能打开 哦,真的,我敢打赌,你不能打开这个
哦,真的,我敢打赌,你不能打开这个
open oh really I bet you can't open this
one aha no problem at all clang clang
一九九九八九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九九
clang here we
我们这里的叮当叮当叮当叮当没有问题
go easy
轻松
peasy another lock huh watch
轻松又一个锁着呢 看着呢
又一个锁着,又一个紧紧的锁,哈哈,手表
peasy another lock huh watch
me huh again open it open it open open
又锁又开又开,又开又开,又开又开,又开又开又开,看我又开又开,又开又开,又开开开
我再次打开它 打开它 打开它打开它
me huh again open it open it open open
what still
我再次打开它 打开它打开它 打开什么
仍然在
what still
more come on what would I can do open
我还能做什么呢?
再来,我还能做什么? 开什么开?
more come on what would I can do open
open
再来,我还能做什么? 开什么开什么开?
打开
open
open wow it's the boss's fish cracker
哇,是老板的鱼饼干
nicely
哇 哇 老板的鱼饼干很好吃
漂亮
nicely
done this mission is for you meow you
完成这个使命 是为了你抚慰你
can trust
完成这个使命 是为了你温柔 你可以信任
me Phantom cats keep causing trouble so
我幽幻猫不断惹麻烦,所以...
we need more patrols
幽灵猫不断制造麻烦 所以我们需要更多的巡逻
我们需要更多的巡逻
we need more patrols
sure finally it's my time to
终于确定我该
shine huh can't open it try
终于确定我该发光了 就不能打开它试试看吗?
发光啊 开不开呀 试试看啊
shine huh can't open it try
another still can't open
发光又不能打开 试另一个还是不能打开
另一只仍然无法打开
another still can't open
it it's got to work this
另一只仍然无法打开它 它必须起作用
一定能行得通的
it it's got to work this
time
这次一定要成功
时间
time
hey who's
时间,嘿嘿,谁
嘿,谁是谁
hey who's
there no one
嘿,谁在那里 没有人
here
在这里
ouch I've trained for 10 years I can
我训练了10年 我可以
open it open open open it no way oh no
10年来我训练了10年 我可以打开它 打开它
开开开开开开开开开开开开开开开开不开开开开开
open it open open open it no way oh no
this is the latest door lock I can't
开开开开开开开开不开门 哦,哦,不,这是最新的门锁,我不行
这是最新的门锁,我不能
this is the latest door lock I can't
open
这是最新的门锁,我无法打开
it watch my shrinking skill let's go
看我的收缩技能,我们走吧
play at my house
看我的收缩技能 让我们去我家玩吧
okay
还好
oops I forgot my key what then we can't
好吧,我忘了我的钥匙,然后我们不能
哦,我忘了我的钥匙,然后我们不能
oops I forgot my key what then we can't
get in I'll tell you a
哦,我忘了我的钥匙... ...然后我们就进不去了... ...我告诉你...
secret Tada look my grandma hides the
秘密塔卡看我外婆藏着
key under the flower pot oh I heard
我奶奶把钥匙藏在花盆下面
花盆下面的钥匙 哦,我听说了
key under the flower pot oh I heard
that well my dad hides the key under the
在花盆下面的钥匙下 哦,我听说我爸把钥匙藏在花盆下面
我爸把钥匙藏在
that well my dad hides the key under the
doorm and my dad hides the key in the
我爸把钥匙藏在门下 我爸把钥匙藏在门下
我爸把钥匙藏在
doorm and my dad hides the key in the
mailbox
门门和我爸把钥匙藏在信箱里
邮箱
mailbox
La no more worries about getting
邮箱La 不再担心得到
不再担心得到
La no more worries about getting
cheese yes come on
不用再担心吃芝士了 来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来
in time to get to
及时到
work hey ha let me see the keys
来得及去上班 嘿哈哈 让我看看钥匙
here h
这里h
it's little Rhino's house the key under
是小犀牛的房子 钥匙在下面
the
这是小犀牛的房子 钥匙在
doorm here it
门关在这里
is there's a
是否有
face a load of goodies off to little
面对着微薄的微薄的佳美的面目,
rabbit
面对着一堆小兔子的美味
house ow that
内有
hurts huh how did this stuff get
这东西是怎么弄成这样子的?
here oh no Phantom cat strike again
这东西是怎么到这里的? 不会再有幽灵猫袭击了
这里没有幽影猫再次出击
here oh no Phantom cat strike again
let's
这里没有幽影猫再次罢工 让我们再次
go the key is
去键是
here need some water
这里需要一些水
uh Thief how did you get
小偷,你是怎么搞到的?
in you left the key outside so it was
你是怎么进来的 把钥匙留在外面的
在你把钥匙留在外面的时候
in you left the key outside so it was
easy to get
在您把钥匙留在了外面,所以很容易得到
容易获得
easy to get
in sweetie who are you talking
容易进入 蜂蜜,谁在说话 谁在说话
在甜甜的甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜
in sweetie who are you talking
to it's a
{\fn黑体\fs22\bord1\shad0\3aHBE\4aH00\fscx67\fscy66\2cHFFFFFF\3cH
是一个
to it's a
face stop
脸部停止
B cat stop if you don't chase me I won't
你不追我,B猫就停,我不会的
run
你不追我,B猫就停,我跑不跑
运行中
run
ouch oh shrinking
运行 触摸 oh 缩缩
skill Catch Me If You
(如果你们能赶上我,那末,你们能赶上我,如果你们能赶上我,
Can let's split
如果你们可以分开,我们就分开吧
散开吧
Can let's split
up can't catch
爬起来抓不着
me stop
停止我停下来
oh
哦
no turn the pipe this way
哦,不转管 这样的方式
管子不往这边转
no turn the pipe this way
okay
还好
hey B cat you're coming with us oh
嘿,B猫,你跟我们一起来哦!
嘿,B猫,你要跟我们一起来哦
hey B cat you're coming with us oh
no Sheriff's
没有警长的
notes things to keep in
没有警长的笔记 保持的东西
要保存的笔记
notes things to keep in
mind kids tell your parents not to hide
孩子们叫你父母别藏起来
孩子们劝你父母不要藏起来
mind kids tell your parents not to hide
easy to find Keys near the door
孩子们别介意孩子们 叫你父母不要躲起来 很容易在门口找到钥匙
容易在门附近找到密钥
easy to find Keys near the door
if a bad person finds them it will be
如果坏人发现门口有钥匙 很容易在门附近找到钥匙
如果一个坏人发现他们,这将是
if a bad person finds them it will be
very
如果坏人发现坏人发现他们...
严格
very
dangerous please remember
非常危险 请记住
that I want to be a
我想成为
drummer I'm
鼓鼓手,我
tired
鼓鼓,我累了
huh huh
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈(哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈
wow that's so
哇,这是如此
cool I want to be an awesome drummer
酷,我想做一个很棒的鼓手
I've been practicing a song with my
我一直在练习一首歌与我的
teacher let me play it for you okay
我和老师一起练了一首歌 让我来弹给你听,好吗?
ouch it wasn't so good was
感觉不是那么好
it it's okay keep practicing and you'll
它不是那么好 是它没关系 继续练习,你会
没关系,继续练习,你会
it it's okay keep practicing and you'll
be as good as your
没关系,继续练习,你会像你一样好
像你一样好
be as good as your
teacher all right I'll try
跟你老师一样好 我试试
again so
再次这样
noisy my ears are
又吵吵吵吵闹的我的耳朵
ringing everybody's run
铃响大家的跑
does it really sound that
这是否真的听起来
bad I'm
这真的听起来真的 听起来,不好的我
我坏,我坏,我坏,我坏
bad I'm
sorry sweetie let's practice the
对不起,亲爱的,让我们练习一下
drum the drum
鼓鼓鼓
set it's gone
# 鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓响起 鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓鼓
装好了,没了
set it's gone
something's
某样东西
up M monkey what happened Sheri lador my
发生什么了? 我的雪莉拉拉着我的
M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M
up M monkey what happened Sheri lador my
daughter's drum set is missing and she
M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M M
女儿的鼓声不见了,她
daughter's drum set is missing and she
loves playing it so
女儿的鼓声不见了,她喜欢玩
喜欢玩它 喜欢玩它
loves playing it so
much don't worry we'll help you find
这么喜欢玩就不用担心 我们会帮你找到的
it the door locks fine and there are no
门锁好锁,没有
climbing marks no one broke
门锁好,没有攀爬痕迹 没人打破
in huh dang how did the drums disappear
鼓声是怎么消失的?
Oops why is the drumstick
鼓声是怎么消失的啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊
哎呀,为什么是鼓棒
Oops why is the drumstick
here what's that
这是什么?
sound I'm going to get
声音声响,我会得到
you steal the
你偷偷
drum no Lulu must have found it and
你偷了鼓 露露一定找到了
没有 露露 一定是找到它了
drum no Lulu must have found it and
thought it was a toy
一定是露露找到的 以为是玩具
found a symbol oh let's keep looking in
找到一个符号哦 让我们继续寻找
the
排
yard oh found another drum and here's
找到了另一个鼓,这里是
another symbol too just one drum left
找到了另一个鼓 还有另一个符号 只剩下一个鼓
另一个符号太太太太 仅剩下一个鼓
another symbol too just one drum left
now where could it
另一个符号太太太太太 只是一个鼓 离开一个鼓 现在在哪里可以它
be huh what's
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈
thisuh yikes it's
{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3cH2F2F2F
依依依依依它
thisuh yikes it's
here oh we found them all thank you so
哦,我们找到他们了,谢谢你
哦,我们找到了他们,谢谢大家
here oh we found them all thank you so
much they were all hidden in the yard
哦,我们找到了他们 非常感谢你们,他们都藏在院子里
大部分都藏在院子里
much they were all hidden in the yard
looks like someone hid them on
都藏在院子里 好像有人藏起来了
看起来像是有人藏起来的
looks like someone hid them on
purpose sister monkey did you hide
有目的的猴子妹妹 你躲了起来吗?
them well yes sorry actually I did
确实很抱歉,实际上我做了
it sweet
是的,对不起 其实我做了甜甜的
它甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜
it sweet
why did you do that I I didn't want to
甜甜,为什么你这样做,我 我不想
你为什么这么做? 我并不想
why did you do that I I didn't want to
learn it anymore I've been trying for
为什么你要那么做? 我不想再学了,我一直在努力
学会了,我一直在努力去学习
learn it anymore I've been trying for
days but still can't play well just for
我已经尝试了好几天了 却仍然无法好好地弹琴
几天,但仍然不能发挥好 仅仅因为
days but still can't play well just for
a few days give us a
几天,但还是不能打好球 仅仅几天,给我们一个
moment oh wow mommy Sheriff Labrador is
哦,哇哦,妈妈妈妈 警长拉布拉多是
the amazing drummer I saw at the store
妈咪拉布拉多警长是我在店里看到的 令人惊叹的鼓手
我在店里看到的 令人惊叹的鼓手
the amazing drummer I saw at the store
wo he's
我在店里看见的惊人的鼓手
# 他 # # 他 # # 他 # # Ww he # #
wo he's
awesome I've been practicing for many
他真棒,我已经练了很多次了
我练习了好多次了
awesome I've been practicing for many
years come on sister
真棒,我练练了好多年了 姐姐,来吧,姐姐
年月来,姐姐
years come on sister
monkey give it a
年复一年吧,姐姐猴子给它一个
猴子给它一个
monkey give it a
try don't rush when playing the drums
打鼓时不要急着打鼓
keep the
玩鼓时不要急着打鼓
保留
keep the
Beats let's do it together
保持"比比比",让我们一起做
我们一起跳吧
Beats let's do it together
that's it follow the
这就是它跟随
beat wow it sounds so
哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇
good great job you're amazing
干得漂亮,你真了不起
yeah sister monkey keep up your drum
干得漂亮,你真棒 猴子姐妹 保持你的鼓声
姐妹猴子 保持你的鼓声
yeah sister monkey keep up your drum
lessons don't give up when it gets
不要放弃 当它得到
教课不会放弃,当它得到
lessons don't give up when it gets
tough I'll keep practicing and play as
教课不放弃,当它变得困难的时候 我会继续练习和玩
我会继续练习和玩
tough I'll keep practicing and play as
great as you
我会跟你一样好好练习打球
和你一样伟大
great as you
sir Sheriff's notes things to keep in
警长的笔记
mind kids when you're learning something
当你学到东西时, 给孩子们打心心
new you'll face difficulties and
当你在学习新东西时 给孩子们打心脑后 你会面临困难和困难
新的你将面临困难
new you'll face difficulties and
challenges
新的你将面临困难和挑战
挑战挑战挑战
challenges
you might want to give up but remember
您也许想放弃挑战, 但记住
您也许想放弃, 但记住
you might want to give up but remember
if there is no
您也许想放弃, 但记住如果没有
如果有否
if there is no
rain there is no
如果没有雨,没有雨,没有雨,没有雨
雨没有雨
rain there is no
rainbow so don't get
雨水没有彩虹,所以不要得到
彩虹,所以不要得到
rainbow so don't get
discouraged keep trying and you can do
彩虹,所以不要灰心灰心 继续尝试,你可以做到
it family emergency
紧急家庭情况
scams 1 2 3 4 two two three four spin
家庭紧急诈骗 12 3 4 4 2 2 3 3 4 旋转
骗骗骗 12 3 4 2 2 2 3 4 旋转
scams 1 2 3 4 two two three four spin
around ending PS yeah and we're all
骗骗骗 12 3 4 4 2 2 3 4
环绕结束PS 是的,我们都
around ending PS yeah and we're all
warmed up
环绕PS的结束 是的,我们都热热身了
time sweetie Mommy needs some water you
亲爱的妈妈需要点水给你喝
go play with the other kids first
亲爱的妈妈需要点水,你先去跟别的孩子玩
先去跟其他孩子一起玩吧
go play with the other kids first
okay water water my
和别的孩子们一起玩吧 先喝水好吗?
water my bad
水 我的坏水 我的坏水
hello ambulance someone got hurt at the
你好 救护车 有人受伤了
sports park please come quickly now I
你好 救护车 有人在体育公园受伤 请快点过来
体育公园,请快来,现在我
sports park please come quickly now I
can trick little
体育公园,请快来,现在我可以小耍小把戏了
mo little mo little mole your mom got
你妈妈的莫小小小内鬼
hurt and she was just taken to the
你妈妈受伤了 她刚被带去
她受伤了 她刚被带去
hurt and she was just taken to the
hospital
她受伤了 她刚被送进医院
医院医院
hospital
Mommy that's not possible she was fine
医院妈妈 这不可能 她很好
妈妈不可能 她没事的
Mommy that's not possible she was fine
just
妈妈这不可能 她很好 只是
只是
just
now mommy little I'm a friend of your
现在妈妈小,我是你的一个朋友
mom come with me to the
现在妈妈小妈妈 我是你妈妈的朋友 跟我来
妈妈跟我去
mom come with me to the
hospital how did she get hurt hope
妈妈跟我去医院,妈妈怎么会有希望?
医院她怎么伤了希望?
hospital how did she get hurt hope
she'll get better
医院她怎么受伤了 希望她会好起来
soon huh Miss Mo I thought you were at
莫小姐,我以为你在
the hospital a I'm not hurt where's my
莫小姐,我以为你在医院 我哪里受伤了?
医院... ...我不受伤... ...我在哪里?
the hospital a I'm not hurt where's my
son someone took him to the hospital to
医院... 我没有受伤... 我儿子在哪里... 有人带他去医院...
儿子,有人带他去医院
son someone took him to the hospital to
find you what
儿子,有人带他去医院找你什么
Sheriff Labrador please help me there's
拉布拉多警长 请帮我
someone claiming to be a friend of Miss
拉布拉多警长,请帮帮我 有人自称是小姐的朋友
有人声称自己是Miss的朋友
someone claiming to be a friend of Miss
mole she took little mole to the
有人声称自己是内奸小姐的朋友 她拿小内奸去
她拿小内鬼去
mole she took little mole to the
hospital saying that his mom got hurt
她带小内鬼去医院 说他妈妈受伤了
医院说他妈妈受伤了
hospital saying that his mom got hurt
that sounds like a scam which way did
医院说他妈妈受伤了 听起来像是骗局
听起来像是骗局
that sounds like a scam which way did
they
听起来像一个骗局 他们是如何做的
和
they
go that
他们走那条路
前进
go that
way let's
走那条路,我们走那条路
以我们的方式
way let's
go Mommy
去吧妈妈
we should hurry come on take it easy
我们快快来,别急,别急
your mom's not at the
我们该快点来 别急 你妈妈不在
hospital but I saw the ambulance going
但我看到救护车开往医院
by it was a lie she wasn't hurt at
医院 但我看到救护车经过时 她没有受伤
她没有被伤害过
by it was a lie she wasn't hurt at
all you tricked
你骗她,她没受伤害
你们所欺骗的,
all you tricked
me
你骗我,骗我
help you can't run away
帮助您无法逃跑
ha found them over
在大地上发现他们,
there
此处
Doby it's antel she's chasing little mo
多比,这是Antel 她追着小莫
what she's causing troubles
多比,这是多比,她正在追逐的小小摩尔 她正在制造麻烦
她制造的麻烦
what she's causing troubles
again according to the photo they went
根据照片,她又惹麻烦了
照他们的照片
again according to the photo they went
that way let's
照片显示他们朝那方向去了
go
上去
stop huh where is he
他现在在哪里?
hiding found
找到隐藏
you help
隐藏发现帮助
帮助您帮助
you help
stop the place SP them all it's okay now
停止停停的地方 SP他们 一切都好,现在没事了
don't be afraid stop right
别怕,别怕,别怕,别怕,别怕,别怕,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别怕,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,停,别停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停,停
不要怕,不要怕,停停右
don't be afraid stop right
there what do I do what do I
不要害怕,站在那里别动,我该怎么办 我做什么,我做什么
在那里,我做什么 我做什么,我做什么
there what do I do what do I
do Grandpa I'm going to buy some candy
爷爷,我要买点糖果
爷爷做爷爷,我要去买糖果
do Grandpa I'm going to buy some candy
okay be
做爷爷,我要去买糖果,好吗?
careful aha I have an idea let me find a
小心点,我有个主意 让我找一个
picture of little turtle yes that's it
小心点,我有个主意 让我找一幅小乌龟的照片
小乌龟的照片 是的,就是这样
picture of little turtle yes that's it
Mr Turtle your grandson got hurt and was
小乌龟的照片 是的,是的,这就是它 乌龟先生 你孙子受伤了
海龟先生 你孙子受伤了
Mr Turtle your grandson got hurt and was
taking into the hospital what he was
海龟先生 你孙子受伤了 正在医院治疗他
将他送进医院
taking into the hospital what he was
fine just now look at this my
刚刚他很好 看看我的这个
刚刚好,看看这个,我的
fine just now look at this my
grandson hurry I'll show you the
孙子快点,我带你去看看
way
方形
okay checked another
重新检查了另一个
one what are you doing Mr Turtle you're
查查另一个,你在做什么 乌龟先生,你是
一个你在做什么 乌龟先生你是
one what are you doing Mr Turtle you're
going the wrong way
一个你在做什么 海龟先生 你走错方向了
走错方向了
going the wrong way
no I'm not I'm taking you to the police
走错方向了 不,不,我不 我不是要带你去报警
不,不,我不是要带你报警
no I'm not I'm taking you to the police
station what oh that's great the police
不,不,我不是要带你 到警察局什么 哦,这是伟大的警察
什么? 哦,这是伟大的警察
station what oh that's great the police
are right
站什么,哦,这是伟大的警察是对的
右对右
are right
there Sheriff Labrador there's a scammer
拉布拉多警长 有个骗子
here she's the one we're looking for oh
拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长
我们要找的就是她
here she's the one we're looking for oh
no stop
在这里,她就是我们要找的人 哦,别停,别停
stop watch my NS
停止看着我的NS
Grandpa my
爷爷我爷爷
sweetie I knew that it was not the
爷爷,我的宝贝爷爷 我知道这不是
亲爱的 我知道这不是
sweetie I knew that it was not the
picture of my grandson look this is our
亲爱的 我知道这不是我孙子的照片
我孙孙子的照片 看,这是我们的
picture of my grandson look this is our
family's traditional shell
这是我孙子的照片 看,这是我们家的传统外壳
padle antel you're coming with us
和我们一起走
Sheriff labrador's safety
拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids some bad people might make up
拉布拉多警长的安全谈话 孩子们 一些坏人可能会编造
和孩子聊天 坏人可能和坏人和解
talk kids some bad people might make up
fake stories to trick us they might say
说些坏人可能编假故事来骗我们 他们可能会说
假故事来欺骗我们 他们可能会说
fake stories to trick us they might say
your family is hurt and in the hospital
假故事来欺骗我们 他们可能会说 你的家人受伤了 在医院里
家人受伤,住院治疗
your family is hurt and in the hospital
or that they've been in a car accident
你的家人受伤了,在医院里,或者他们遭遇了车祸
或者他们遭遇了车祸
or that they've been in a car accident
don't believe what they say and never go
或者他们遭遇了车祸 不相信他们说的话 永不去
不相信他们说的话,永不离去
don't believe what they say and never go
with them call your parents or the
不要相信他们说的话 也不要和他们一起去 打电话给你的父母或父母
或召你们的父母,或召你们的父母,
with them call your parents or the
police right away please remember that
和他们一起打电话给你父母或警察 请记住
police takes care of a
警方负责照顾
baby Doby time to get
婴儿 Doby 时间到
off oh no I'm late I'm
哦,不,我迟到了,我迟到了
late oh no oh
哦,不,不,不,不,不
no comeing have breakfast huh same as
哦,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不
不来不来就吃早饭 和不来不来吃早饭一样
no comeing have breakfast huh same as
yesterday this this and this these are
和昨天一样吃早餐 这个和这个
昨天的这个和这个 这些是
yesterday this this and this these are
all your
昨天这个和这个都是你的
对你所有
all your
favorites mom I really need to go
你所有最喜爱的妈妈 我真的得走了
最喜爱的妈妈,我真的很需要去
favorites mom I really need to go
wait it's so yummy unlike my mom's
等等,它很美味 不像我妈妈的
breakfast which I'm tired of eating your
和我妈的早餐不同,我吃你吃得烦了
早餐,我厌倦了吃你的早餐
breakfast which I'm tired of eating your
mom works hard to make you breakfast she
我厌倦了吃你母亲的早餐 努力工作让你吃早餐
妈妈辛苦工作给你做早餐
mom works hard to make you breakfast she
would be sad if she heard you say
妈妈辛苦工作给你做早餐 她会伤心的,如果她听到你说
如果她听到你说
would be sad if she heard you say
that ow my stomach
我肚子里那恶心的肚子
hurts watch
我肚子的肚子疼 手表
out my baby
出出出我的宝贝
oh I'll take her to the
我带她去
hospital but my
我会送她去医院,但我
但我的医院
hospital but my
baby baby seting is a piece of cake
医院,但我的宝宝 婴儿布置是一个小菜一碟
婴儿婴儿布置是小菜一碟
baby baby seting is a piece of cake
leave it to
婴儿婴儿设置是一块蛋糕,留给
留给
leave it to
us thanks I appreciate
留给我们吧,谢谢,谢谢,我很感激
it sweetie we'll take care of you
亲爱的 我们会照顾你的
today where's the
甜心,我们今天会照顾你的
今日何地
today where's the
baby the baby is
今天婴儿在哪里? 婴儿在哪里? 婴儿在哪里?
婴儿是婴儿
baby the baby is
missing baby get go baby
宝宝 婴儿失踪 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿 婴儿
婴儿失踪 婴儿失踪 婴儿失踪 婴儿失踪 婴儿失踪 婴儿失踪 婴儿失踪 婴儿失踪 婴儿失踪 婴儿失踪 婴儿失踪 婴儿失踪 婴儿失踪 婴儿失踪 婴儿失踪 婴儿失踪
missing baby get go baby
gecko pH Doby baby gecko is on your
失踪的婴儿 得到去婴儿壁虎PH多比 婴儿壁虎是你的
back it's so
背着它是如此
T you can't put this in your
你不能把这个放进你的
mouth baby gecko must be
宝宝的口腔壁虎 一定是
hungry here you go
肚子饿的在这里,你走吧
thank you so much
非常感谢你
officers what is he
军官们,他是什么人呢?
crying are you
官官,他哭什么哭什么哭,你哭什么?
你们在哭泣吗?
crying are you
hungry hey look a
你饿吗? 哭着哭着,你饿了吗?
看着,看看
hungry hey look a
toy let me
饿饿肚子的喂 看着一个玩具 让我来
玩具 让我来
toy let me
try he's
试试他
laughing why is he
他笑着笑着为什么他
为什么他笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着笑着
laughing why is he
crying oh he
呼呼呼呼着他
poop all
屎都拉屎了
done it's a thief a
是一个小偷a
thief
盗贼
W it
盗贼W它
W 时
W it
stinks police oh oh stop right
臭警察的臭警察 哦 哦 停下 停下
臭臭警察 哦 哦 停下右转
stinks police oh oh stop right
there oh no oh looks like he needs
臭臭警察 哦 哦 停在那儿 哦 不 哦 看起来他需要
哦,不,不,哦,看起来他需要
there oh no oh looks like he needs
help here you
在这里帮助您
go
上去
hey hey you can't run
嘿嘿嘿嘿 你不能跑
away hey stop
嘿嘿嘿嘿 你不能跑开 停下
watch out where's
当心,当心
Wolf the handbag is here he's probably
狼的手提包在这里,他可能在这里
not far huh where is he
狼的手提包在这里 他可能不远,他在哪里?
hiding all right all right I'm going to
藏起来,藏起来,藏起来 好,我要去
pick it
藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好藏好我我我我我我我我我 我由由由由由由由由由由由由由由我 我由我 我由我 我由由由我 我由我 我由我 我由我 我由由我 我由由我我我取
选它
pick it
up gotch you
高高的你 高高的你
gotcha
来啦 来啦 来啦 来啦
huh oh I got
呵呵,我得到了
it I got you nobody can run away from
我得到了你 没有人可以逃避
me baby gecko you helped us a lot
我亲爱的壁虎 你帮了我们很多忙
sweetie he's
亲爱的,他
asleep thank you for taking care of my
谢谢你照顾我
baby it's our
谢谢你照顾我的宝宝 这是我们的
宝宝,这是我们的
baby it's our
pleasure goodbye bye babysitting is not
宝宝,这是我们的快乐 我们的快乐,再见再见 再见 保姆是不是
快乐的再见,再见 保姆是不是
pleasure goodbye bye babysitting is not
easy that's right being parents is not
做父母的权利不是 做父母的权利不是
做父母是件容易的事 做父母不是件容易的事
easy that's right being parents is not
easy Doby I'm here why did you get up so
多比,我在这里,为什么你起来了?
early because I wanted to have breakfast
多比,我在这里 为何你这么早起床 因为我想吃早餐
因为我想早早早早点吃早餐
early because I wanted to have breakfast
with you H here you
早早是因为我想和你吃早餐 H在这里,你在这里
与你同H在这里,你在这里
with you H here you
go Sheriff labrador's safety
去拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids being parents and raising
去拉布拉多警长的安全谈话 孩子们做父母和抚养
谈论孩子做父母和抚养子女
talk kids being parents and raising
children is very hard work you should
和孩子做父母 抚养孩子是很辛苦的工作 你应该
孩子是非常勤劳的工作 你应该
children is very hard work you should
appreciate what your parents do for you
孩子很勤勤劳,你应该体谅你父母为你做的一切
感激你父母为你做的一切
appreciate what your parents do for you
and love them even more
感激你父母为你做的一切 更深爱他们
fishing
渔业
Adventure daddy why isn't the fish
冒险爸爸 为什么鱼不是鱼
biting yet fishing rule number one
冒险爸爸 为什么鱼不咬鱼 却没钓鱼第一规则呢
钓鱼规则一
biting yet fishing rule number one
patience and number
钓鱼规则第1号 耐心和数量
和 数 和 数 、 数、 数、 数、 数、 数、 数、 数、 数、 数、 数、 数、 数、 数、 数、 数、 数、 数、 数、 数、 数、 数、 数
patience and number
two oh no I need the
和二号的耐心 哦,不,我需要
bathroom
卫生间卫生间
ouch son fishing roll number two kids
2个孩子的钓鱼卷
子钓鱼卷二号孩子
ouch son fishing roll number two kids
shouldn't fish
2号鱼卷 2号孩子不应该钓鱼 2号鱼卷 孩子不应该钓鱼
不应该钓鱼
shouldn't fish
alone got it oh the fish but kids
鱼不能只吃鱼啊 鱼啊 鱼啊 小孩啊
独自一人得到它哦,鱼,但孩子
alone got it oh the fish but kids
shouldn't fish alone wait for Daddy to
鱼儿不能独自钓鱼 等爸爸来
鱼不能只吃鱼 等爸爸来
shouldn't fish alone wait for Daddy to
come
鱼不能独自钓鱼 等爸爸来
back no no what do I
没有没有没有没有,没有没有什么,我该怎么办?
do it's getting
不,不,不,不,我做什么 我做什么,它得到
away daddy
离爸爸( D)
hurry I can't hold
爸爸快点,我抱不住了
it I can't see anything
我什么都看不见
help Daddy's back la la la la la I can't
帮助爸爸回来啦啦啦啦 我不能
get this
帮助爸爸回来啦啦啦啦啦 我拿不下这个
off son where's my son sweetie where are
儿子在哪里 我儿子在哪里 亲爱的在哪里
you something's wrong over there let's
我的儿子在哪里 亲爱的 你哪里出问题了?
你出事了,我们来
you something's wrong over there let's
go Mr Cat what happened Sheriff Labrador
拉布拉多警长,我们走吧,凯特先生
凯特先生,拉布拉多警长 发生了什么事?
go Mr Cat what happened Sheriff Labrador
please help while I was in the bathroom
卡特先生,请帮我一下 我在洗手间的时候 帮帮忙,拉布拉多警长
我在洗手间的时候,拜托你帮我一下
please help while I was in the bathroom
my son went missing
我在洗手间时请帮忙 我儿子失踪了
I think I heard little cat say it's a
我好像听到小猫咪说
fish
我好像听到小猫说是鱼
what the rod is gone oh no he might have
哦,不,他也许有
been dragged Away by the
他也许被牵着走
被拖着走在路上,
been dragged Away by the
fish doy Let's
被鱼狗拖走
Go sir over there
先生,去那边
it's little
先生,去那边,小一点的
cat let's
猫猫,让我们
hurry
快点
yay ouch
哟啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊
party party
政党党党
party Ribbit who's being so rude I'm
Ribbit的党 谁是那么粗鲁,我是谁
sorry I can't
Ribbit的派对,谁的 如此粗鲁,对不起,我不能
stop oh
停止哦
no so dizzy
没有这么头晕
help me Doby we need to speed up watch
帮我多比,我们得加快手表的进度
me
我,我,我
ouch oh no there's a
啊,哦,不,有一个
waterfall watch
水瀑观察
out Sher Labrador it's okay you're safe
舍尔拉布拉多,没事的,你安全了
now that was really
谢尔拉布拉多,没关系 你现在安全了,那真的
现在,这是真的
now that was really
close why is the log
现在真的很接近了,为什么日志
关闭为什么为日志
close why is the log
moving be careful it's a
关闭为什么日志移动要小心 它是一个
动作要小心,它是一个
moving be careful it's a
crocodile crocodile
小心点,这是鳄鳄鱼
don't worry I can hold
别担心,我可以撑得住
on we're
我们...
surrounded
包围
run you'll never bite
环环环环环环绕的奔跑,你永远不会咬人
跑跑,你永远不会咬
run you'll never bite
me
跑跑,你永远不会咬我
我,我,我
me
ouch let's get out of
# 我触摸我,让我们离开#
here uh-oh the money's so sticky huh oh
这里啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊
no the crocodiles are
这里啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊 鳄鱼啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊 鳄鱼啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊 鳄鱼啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊
coming this
来来来来来来来来来来来
way I'm up high now you can't bite
高高高高高高的我 让你不能咬人
me oops I got
这样我爬高了,你就不能咬我
shorter Toby run to the
更短的托比跑到
shore hey
向上
don't chase
不要追,不要追
me
我,我,我
Doby grab
多比抓我,多比抓我
多比抢抢
Doby grab
on glad that's
很高兴
over
很高兴一切都结束了
超过
over
s Daddy I won't fish Alone Again
爸爸我不会再独自钓鱼了
爸爸,我不会再独自钓鱼了
s Daddy I won't fish Alone Again
Sheriff labrador's safety
拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids you shouldn't fish
说小孩你不应该钓鱼
alone if you get poked by a sharp
说小孩你不应该独自钓鱼 如果你被尖锐的刺穿
如果你被一个锐利的人戳穿,
alone if you get poked by a sharp
hook or fall into the water it can be
如果你被一个尖钩戳到 或掉入水中 独自一人
或掉入水中
hook or fall into the water it can be
very
或掉入水中 可能非常
严格
very
dangerous you might even lose your lives
非常危险 你甚至可能失去生命
危险,甚至可能失去生命
dangerous you might even lose your lives
always go fishing with grown-ups for
你甚至可能失去生命 危险你甚至可能失去你的生命 总是去钓鱼 与成年人
总是跟大人去钓鱼
always go fishing with grown-ups for
your own safety please remember
一定要跟大人去钓鱼 是为了自己安全,请记住
请记住您自己的安全
your own safety please remember
that
请记住:
,该数额,
that
left dangerous has fallen power
危险左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左左右下下
左左危险势力倒下 左危险势力倒下 左危险 左危险 左危险 左危险 左危险 左危险 左危险 左危险
left dangerous has fallen power
lines
左左危险线 输下电线
R let's go my big
R,我们走,我的大
Dino huh what's that
迪诺,那是什么?
sound what's
声音的音响
that w there's smoke coming out what's
烟雾从烟雾中冒出来 烟雾从烟雾中喷出 烟雾从烟雾中喷出
WW有烟 冒出什么
that w there's smoke coming out what's
going
WW有烟 冒出烟 正在发生什么
on
上 年 月
help something's wrong
帮助某事是错的
what's wrong with the dinos watch
迪诺表有什么问题?
me
我,我,我
labador there's a thin and long monster
有个瘦长的怪物
making crackling sounds over there and
那边有个瘦长的怪兽 在那里发出怪声
在那里发出怪声
making crackling sounds over there and
it's glowing too our Dino started acting
我们的迪诺开始演戏了
weird after touching
这太发光了 我们的迪诺在接触后开始怪怪怪的
it how is that possible I'll go take a
怎么会这样,我会去 采取一个
look I'm coming with
怎么会这样呢? 我该去看一眼
看我,我来了
look I'm coming with
you looks like it got burnt a thin long
你看起来像是被烧了那么长
and crackling monster could it be oh no
你看起来像它被烧了 薄薄的长长和怪怪怪怪怪的 会不会是哦
和疯狂的怪兽 会不会是哦,不
and crackling monster could it be oh no
Doby and papion might be in danger
多比和Papion可能处于危险之中
the crackling
sound it must be
一定是那怪怪的怪声
nearby Doby over there stop right
附近多比在那边停车
there my feet are numb what's going on
在那里,我的脚麻麻了 发生了什么事
let me help you
在那里,我的脚麻麻了 发生了什么事 让我帮你
让我来帮你
let me help you
don't there might be electricity around
让我来帮你 周围可能没有电
周围没有电源吗?
don't there might be electricity around
Doby
多比附近可能没有电
多比
Doby
electricity Doby put your legs
多比把腿放好
多比把腿放上电
electricity Doby put your legs
together now hop over to me like a
一起跳到我身边
bunny like a
像兔子一样的兔子
bunny Labrador what's going on I suppose
兔子拉布拉多 这是怎么回事 我猜
that long thin and crackling monster
兔子拉布拉多 这是怎么回事,我想 长薄和怪兽
长长薄的怪兽
that long thin and crackling monster
that the kids mentioned is a power line
孩子们提到的长长的瘦长的怪兽 是一条电线
孩子们提到的是电线
that the kids mentioned is a power line
a power line mhm when a power line
上面提到的小孩是电线 当电线时是电线 mhm
当电线为电线时, 电线为mhm
a power line mhm when a power line
touches the ground it electrifies the
当电线碰到地面时,电线使电线通电。
与它所使电动的地面交接,
touches the ground it electrifies the
ground nearby and if you come close your
与地面接触时,它使附近地面通电,如果你们靠近,
附近地面附近,如果你靠近你的
ground nearby and if you come close your
feet will feel numb in that case you
附近地面附近,如果你靠近,你的脚将感到麻木 那样的话,你将感到麻木
如果那样,你将感到麻木,
feet will feel numb in that case you
need to put your legs together and hop
脚将感到麻木 在这样的情况下,你需要 把你的腿合起来,跳
需要把双腿放在一起跳
need to put your legs together and hop
away just like a bunny or else your life
需要把双腿放在一起 和像兔子一样跳走 否则你的生活
象兔子一样离开,否则你的生命
away just like a bunny or else your life
might be in danger and if you see
象兔子一样离开,否则你的生命可能会有危险 如果你看到
可能处于危险之中 如果你看到
might be in danger and if you see
someone get shocked don't touch them or
如果你看到有人受到惊吓 千万别碰他们
被震惊的人 不要碰他们,或
someone get shocked don't touch them or
you'll get shocked
被震惊的人 不要碰他们 否则你会被惊吓的
你会被吓到的
you'll get shocked
too that was close
差一点,你也会被吓到的
那也太近了
too that was close
we need to find the power line now to
现在我们需要找到电线
我们现在需要找到电线
we need to find the power line now to
prevent further
我们需要找到电线 以进一步防止
进一步防止
prevent further
accidents little won show time little
零赢的场景时间
won find the Fallen power line around
中小赢 显示时间 中小赢 找到堕落的电线 周围
找到周围的堕落电线
won find the Fallen power line around
here
在这里找到堕落的电线
t
t 时
t t
吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨吨
oh no the telephone call is about to
哦,没有电话 电话是即将到
fall we need to evacuate everyone right
哦,没有电话是即将下降的 电话是即将下降 我们需要疏散每个人的权利
now here's your balloon yay
这是你的气球耶
Watch
监视监视观察
Out Hold On To Me
坚持我
that was so
是这样
scary Sheriff labrador's safety
可怕的警长拉布拉多的安全
talk kids when you see a fallen power
当你看到一股衰落的力量时,
line on the ground make sure to stay
当你看到地面上停电线倒塌时 和孩子们聊天 一定要留下来
现场的线条 一定要留在原地
line on the ground make sure to stay
away from it if you happen to enter an
在地面的线条上,如果您碰巧进入
进入火狱者,若不入火狱,
away from it if you happen to enter an
electrified area and your feet feel some
如果你的脚碰巧进入一个电气化的地区,而感觉有些烦闷,那末,(此处叩头!)
电子化区域 和你的脚感觉一些
electrified area and your feet feel some
don't go any further lift one foot or
电化区和你的脚感觉有些 不再往前抬,一脚或一脚或一脚
不准再往下抬 一只脚或
don't go any further lift one foot or
put your legs together and hop away from
不要再往前抬一脚 或把腿放在一起,然后跳离开
双腿齐齐,跳起舞来,
put your legs together and hop away from
there just like a
双腿合起来,从那跳下去 就像跳起来一样
在那里,就像一个
there just like a
bunny if you see someone get shocked you
在那里就像兔子一样,如果你看到有人震惊你
兔子,如果你看到有人让你震惊
bunny if you see someone get shocked you
should never go near them you should ask
兔子,如果你看到有人被惊吓 你不应该靠近他们,你应该问
你不要临近他们,你应当问他们,
should never go near them you should ask
adults for help please remember these
千万不要靠近他们,你应该求大人帮忙 请记住这些
tips the shoe biting escalator
向鞋咬取扶梯提示
oh oh kids be
哦,孩子们哦
careful
仔细小心
look kids where are
看着孩子,看孩子在哪里
you m
你 m 个
it smells so
你闻起来好臭
闻闻闻闻闻闻闻闻闻
it smells so
good
闻起来好香香
ouch oh I'm so sorry I didn't mean it
对不起,我不是故意的
are you all right Miss squirrel are you
对不起,我不是说你没事 松鼠小姐是你
你没事吗? 松松鼠小姐是你吗?
are you all right Miss squirrel are you
in a rush oh sheriff Labrador my
松松鼠小姐,你是在赶时间吗? 哦,拉布拉多警长,我的
拉布拉多警长 我的
in a rush oh sheriff Labrador my
children are missing please help me find
拉布拉多警长 我的孩子们失踪了 请帮我找到
孩子们失踪了 请帮我找找
children are missing please help me find
them we're on it
孩子们失踪了 请帮我找到他们 我们正在查
他们正在调查
them we're on it
excuse me have you seen two little
对不起,你见过两个小男孩吗?
squirrels around about this
对不起,你见过两只小松鼠吗?
松松鼠周围 关于这个
squirrels around about this
tall I just saw them at the
松鼠周围的松鼠 大约这个高 我刚刚看到他们在
高高高高,我刚刚看到他们
tall I just saw them at the
aquarium thank you
我刚刚在水族馆看见他们,谢谢
Doby let's split up
多比,我们分开吧
here little squirrels little squirrels
多比,我们分开吧 小松鼠小松鼠小松鼠
小松鼠在这里 小松鼠在这里 小松鼠
here little squirrels little squirrels
little
这里的小松鼠小松鼠小
小
little
squirrels little squirrels
小松鼠 小松鼠 小松鼠
aha I found
我发现
you wrong person
认错人的人
oh no my
哦,不,不,我的
paintings thank goodness they're all
感谢上帝的绘画,他们全都是
safe oh this painting what do you think
谢天谢地,他们都是安全的 哦,这幅画,你觉得怎么样?
这幅画,你觉得呢?
safe oh this painting what do you think
nice huh wow are these two monsters
哦,这幅画安全,你觉得这幅画 是什么,你觉得漂亮,哈哇,是这两个怪兽
哇,这两个怪兽真是好样的
nice huh wow are these two monsters
fighting under a waterfall no
这两个怪兽在瀑布下战斗
oh these are two little squirrels on an
哦,这是两只小松鼠
escalator that's right you have good
哦,这是两个小松鼠 在扶梯上,这是对的 你有好
扶梯,没错,你有好的
escalator that's right you have good
eyes they should still be there let's
扶梯,没错,你有好眼睛 他们应该仍然在那里,让我们
他们的眼睛应该还在那里,让我们
eyes they should still be there let's
go there they are
他们在那里,他们在那里
I
一一
won my shoe is
我的鞋是赢的
stuck watch out
坚持要当心
sweetie thank you Sheriff
亲爱的,谢谢你,警长
Labrador kids playing on the escalator
谢谢你 拉布拉多警长 孩子们在扶梯上玩
拉布拉多小孩在扶梯上玩
Labrador kids playing on the escalator
is very dangerous and you could get hurt
拉布拉多小孩玩扶梯 是很危险的,你会受伤的
十分危险,你可能会受伤
is very dangerous and you could get hurt
I'm sorry we'll never do that
非常危险 而且你可能会受伤 很抱歉我们永远不会这么做
again Sheriff Labrador safety
拉布拉多治安官再次安全
talk kids you should only take an
说话的小孩,你应该只吃
escalator with your
说话的小孩,你应该只 使用一个扶梯 与你的
与您的
escalator with your
parents and never play around while
和父母一起扶扶梯 暂时不玩
父母不以游戏为乐,不以游戏为乐,
parents and never play around while
standing on it in case of an
父母不依父母而游戏,而当父母与父母在一起的时候,他们不依父母和父母而起立,
遇一种情况时,可以靠它站立,
standing on it in case of an
emergency press the emergency stop
遇有紧急新闻记者 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站
紧急紧急按紧急停
emergency press the emergency stop
button and the escalator will stop right
按紧急紧急按钮按紧急停止按钮, 扶梯将右停
按钮,自动扶梯将右停
button and the escalator will stop right
away please remember remember
按钮,自动扶梯将立刻停止,请记住
请记住,请记住,请记住
away please remember remember
that little mole is
请记住,小内鬼是
missing sweetie these fruits are good
亲爱的,这些水果很好吃
for your
少了甜甜,这些水果对你有好处
eyes are you using your tablet again
你的眼睛又在用平板电脑吗?
you're already shortsighted no more
你的眼睛是不是又在用平板电脑了 你已经是短视了
你已经是短视了
you're already shortsighted no more
tablets
你已经是短视了,没有药片了
平板块
tablets
okay let's go
好,我们走吧
please
请
stop sweetie where did he go little mo
停下来,亲爱的,他去了哪里
Little
停下来,亲爱的,他去了哪里? 小莫小
M my glasses
我的眼镜M
they're
我的眼镜
broken
缺 数
mommy he's my
破碎的妈妈 他是我的
妈妈,他是我的
mommy he's my
daddy where's your mommy
妈妈 他是我爸爸 你妈妈在哪
爸爸,你的妈妈在哪?
daddy where's your mommy
kid
爸爸,你的妈妈孩子在哪?
儿童 儿童
kid
Mommy it's
妈妈,是妈妈
Mommy Mommy wait
妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪 妈咪
Little Miss Mo what's going on Sheriff
小莫莫小姐 发生什么事了 警长
labador my child is
小莫小莫小姐 发生什么事了 警长拉玛多尔 我的孩子
拉玛多·拉玛多 我的孩子
labador my child is
missing little more I saw him getting on
我女儿失踪了 我看见他上路了
我看见他上路了
missing little more I saw him getting on
the bus just now oh my goodness let's go
我看见他上巴士了 刚刚哦,我的天啊,我们走吧
刚才的公交车 哦,我的天啊,我们走吧
the bus just now oh my goodness let's go
find him
刚才的公交车 哦我的老天,我们去找他吧
找到他 找到他 找到他
find him
mommy this is the last stop Forest
妈妈,这里是森林最后的一站
Harbor
港端
Mommy
海港妈妈妈妈
妈咪妈妈妈妈
Mommy hi cream
妈咪喜奶奶油
mommy are you going to buy me some ice
妈妈喜奶奶油 妈妈 你要给我买冰冰吗?
妈妈,你要给我买冰冰吗?
mommy are you going to buy me some ice
cream what are you talking about this is
妈妈,你要给我买冰淇淋吗? 你在说什么?
奶油奶油 你在说什么 这是
cream what are you talking about this is
a
奶油奶油 你在说什么 这是
a a/
a
bathroom
洗手间
bathroom you're not mommy oh my tummy
洗手间 你不是妈妈 哦我的肚子
oh it's
哦,这是
stins Mommy where are you oh I need to
妈妈,你在哪里? 哦,我需要
go
妈妈,你在哪里? 哦,我得走了
上去
go
little mo he's not here not here
小莫,他不在这里,不在这里
either are you all right Mr Raccoon have
莱孔先生
you seen little mo little moall he
莱孔先生 你见过他吗?
你看见他,你看见他,你看见他,你看见他,你看见他,
you seen little mo little moall he
headed to the harbor oh no he might be
你看见他去港湾的小小呻吟吗? 哦,不,他可能是
前往港港 哦,不,他可能
headed to the harbor oh no he might be
in Danger let's
不,他可能在危险中,让我们
go Mommy where are
妈咪,你去哪儿了?
you Mommy
妈妈,妈妈,妈妈,妈妈,妈妈到哪里去? 妈妈,妈妈,妈妈,妈妈,妈妈,妈妈,妈妈到哪里去?
mommy no don't close doors are closing
妈妈不要关门,妈妈不要关门,妈妈要关门了
air conditioner on so
妈妈不关不关门 妈妈不关不关门就关了空调
如此的空调机空调机
air conditioner on so
cold little let's split up
这么冷的空调,我们分开吧
寒冷的,我们分开吧
cold little let's split up
here little mo little
寒冷的小家伙,让我们分开在这里 一点点一点一点一点
在这里一点点一点一点一点
here little mo little
mo little mo help somebody help me huh
来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊
来人帮帮我啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊
mo little mo help somebody help me huh
over
来人帮帮我啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊
there look at that it's a little B's bag
看那里,这是个小B的包包
let's
看那里,这是个小B的包包,我们走吧
go I'm so cold oh no the ship's leaving
我太冷了,哦,没有船要离开
hurry
我太冷了,没有船的离开 匆匆离开
快点
hurry
that's it
就是这样
Doby
多比
hey we need to hurry throw me
嘿,我们得快点把我扔出去
over
嘿,我们得快点把我扔过去
okay little
还好小
more officer Doby I'm Sheriff Labrador
多比警官 我是拉布拉多警长
sherff Labrador safety
Sherff 拉布拉多人安全
talk kids your eyes are very important
拉布拉多安全谈话的孩子们 你的眼睛非常重要
和孩子说话 你的眼睛很重要
talk kids your eyes are very important
never look at electronic devices for a
你的眼睛非常重要 永远不要看电子设备
从未看过电子设备
never look at electronic devices for a
long time and don't read or write under
很久从不看电子设备,也不读写
长长的时间,不阅读或写作
long time and don't read or write under
dim
长长的时间, 不要在暗暗下读写
暗暗暗
dim
light also don't rub your eyes with
暗光也用不着擦擦眼睛
也不要用光擦擦眼睛
light also don't rub your eyes with
dirty hands it might hurt your
光也不要用肮脏的手摸你的眼睛 那样会伤害你
脏脏脏的手 可能会伤到你
dirty hands it might hurt your
eyes please keep your eyes healthy by
脏手脏手脏手脏 眼睛可能受伤 请保持眼睛健康
请保持双眼健康
eyes please keep your eyes healthy by
practicing these tips every
眼睛请保持健康 每天练习这些小费
每天练习这些提示
practicing these tips every
day woof
每天练习这些小技巧
白日呼呼
day woof
本字幕由AI大模型生成